[music]
All right.
Um, wow. It's a little weird cuz I
represented myself on this deal. So, um,
I'm I'm very thankful to be able to, uh,
play for this city, uh, play for this
organization, suit up for with my
teammates, for my teammates. Um there's
no workplace I'd rather be. And so uh to
have an opportunity to be able to be
here for another uh two seasons outside
of this year, um it's uh very special.
It means a lot to me and my family.
>> How important was it for you going into
this offseason to get an extension done
so you knew you were going to be here
after playing in multiple places? Yeah,
you know, it was important to me because
uh I just want to be able to focus on
ball and uh you know, having that
security there uh just in terms of the
number of years that that I'm here, it
allows me to just focus on that and um
you know, my main reason for wanting to
get this deal done too is is I just want
to win, you know, and uh I think it's
one less thing on my plate, one less
thing on their plate.
>> How much haggling was there in
negotiations and how good of a
negotiator were you think?
>> Uh I mean I feel like I was pretty good
uh overall, man. Um it was it was uh
went very smooth uh in my opinion. I
feel like uh you know just the way that
our front office handled things and
ownership made it a lot easier on me
representing myself. So um yeah I feel I
feel really good about about the whole
process. how you approach it. It's
called Duke or what? You know what?
>> Yeah.
>> Funny. It it's it's uh it's unique, but
um yeah, a lot of my conversations were
with uh Steve and so um you know, Steve
handled you know, pretty much you know,
I guess the the point man through all of
this and uh allowing allowing everything
to just fall in place. Um and uh he was
really really the main main person that
I handled with and I'm pretty sure that
he was, you know, obviously talking to
Duke and ownership in between. Why was
repping yourself an important? Is that
was that an important thing? And why how
did that decision to to do that in
general? [clears throat]
>> Yeah, you know, to be honest, man, I
think uh just kind of where we are in
today's age of the NFL. Um and also I
think who who I play for, you know, I
think uh representing myself made a lot
of sense in this situation. You know, I
I is this something that I would do
anywhere else? I don't know, you know,
to be honest with you. But uh you know I
think just with my relationship that I
have with our front office and ownership
uh it made a lot of sense.
>> When did the whole process start as far
as when you had started conversations
about the extension?
>> Yeah. Um gosh I I think um first
conversation was sometime in February.
So I believe early February I think was
a was the first uh conversation on it.
Did you view free agency as a deadline
to get it done or did you think once
free agency started it may not get done?
>> Uh, no. I just I I I really wasn't
necessarily too concerned with that, you
know, I just uh just [snorts] wanted to
present it to them and uh I didn't know
if that was going to get done in August
or, you know, July or [clears throat] um
you know, we just so happened to find a
number that we settled on pretty early.
>> You mentioned winning and it
[clears throat] being such a factor for
you. How confident are you that you guys
can figure this out, turn it around and
win this year? Yeah, I'm very confident,
man. Um, you know, we we've got a lot of
special players and a lot of special men
in our locker room and so a lot of
responsibility falls on us to make sure
that we take those next steps as a team.
Uh, you know, I think for for what it's
worth, uh, there are no coaches, there
are no front office execs, no owners
that that step on the field on Sunday.
And so, uh, at the end of the day, a lot
of responsibility falls on us as players
to be able to get the most out of the
locker room, you know, and it starts
with me as a leader, one of the leaders
here. Um, you know, we got one of the
hardest pieces of the puzzle with Joe
Burrow. And so, uh, I think it's
important for everybody else around him,
uh, including myself, to, you know, step
up, step up to the plate.
>> What was Joe's reaction to your
exception?
>> Yeah, he's pretty happy. So, he's pretty
happy.
>> Consistency on the offensive line. I
mean, this seems like a huge thing for
this organization, Orlando, and you're a
big part of that. How important is that?
>> Uh, very important. you know, just being
able to continue to grow um you know,
amongst each other, continuing to grow
our continuity between each other. Uh
you know, our five that we rolled out
there, man, including Dalton at Right
Guard, uh that group um was special. And
you know, I think of some of the other
men in there with Jaylen Rivers, uh
Cody, um you know, Andrew Coker, uh
Javon, um I mean, even some of the guys
we lost like CV and Kirk, uh you know, I
think it's just it's so important and so
special that what what we started there
and and uh you know, just being able to
come back and work with them means a
lot.
>> What did you think of Trey going to the
Ravens?
>> I think it's great. Yeah, I think it's
great. Um you know, I'm happy for him.
He earned that contract. Uh, you know,
it's a great situation for him, and we
get to see him twice a year. So,
>> you get to see him twice a year.
>> I do. Yeah.
>> What do you anticipate [clears throat]
that will be like?
>> Yeah. Um, it'll be a lot of fun. So,
we've had a lot of battles over the
years and, uh, some really big games
when I was in Kansas City. So, um, it'll
be a lot of fun.
>> I mean, you guys kind of notably fought
each other the first time you practiced
against each other.
>> Yeah.
>> Do you do you anticipate it to be like a
kind of a brawl out there against Trey
in that regard? Yeah, I mean I think it
just just kind of just our approach to
the game of football, man. It's uh who
he is. Uh I think about the first time I
played him when I was in Kansas City in
that AFC Championship. To be honest, we
fought there, too. But [laughter]
but uh you know, I think um you know,
that's just the way our approach is and
uh I'm sure the the film will reflect
that when we suit up.
>> Obviously, you're a fan of the NFL. You
follow it really closely. What was your
reaction to the Max situation and Trey
within 12 hours or whatever it was?
>> Well, yeah. No, I mean it's interesting,
man. Uh, you know, to representing
myself, you know, I think you find out a
little bit more about the business side
of things, uh, than you expect to. And,
uh, you know, it's a unique situation. I
I'm I I don't have all the details on
everything, but, you know, I I imagine
it's it's a little bit awkward for the
Ravens and Max Crosby.
>> For for a guy who's played
>> Sorry.
>> For guys who have played against each
other,
>> who's got the edge, the offense, and the
defense, [laughter]
>> you know, that's hard to say. Um, but I
will tell you, uh, I'm excited to kick
some ass. So, I I don't really care who
I'm lining up against, but, um, I I
don't know who the edge goes through,
but but I'm excited for the match up.
>> How big was it for you last year to play
in all 17 games after
>> Yeah.
>> playing really helped you throughout
your career and then you had a couple
injuries your first couple?
>> Yeah. No, that was that was really
important to me, man. Um, you know,
anytime that I can be available, that's
something I pride myself on. And, uh,
you know, uh, anytime that, you know,
I'm able to go out there and suit up on
Sunday, I I want to I want to go play.
So,
>> when you look at your career starting
Baltimore to Kansas City here, do you
feel like your time in Cincinnati has
brought out the best in you in terms of
your performance on the field?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I feel I feel as though um
this is the probably the most
uncomfortable and comfortable situation
for me. Uh in a way, you know, what I'm
asked to do um game to game is is uh
unique in terms of the drop back pass
and one-on-one pass protection. It is
the most vulnerable state for any
offensive lineman in [clears throat]
football, let alone a left tackle. And
uh you add in blocking for a half a
billion dollar quarterback. Um, you
know, and playing for this organization
with great players like Andrew Woodworth
and Anthony Munoz and Willie Anderson,
uh, it comes with a lot of pressure,
but, you know, for me, I I love I love
being a Bengal. I love playing playing
here in this city. Um, you know, I feel
like my best football is ahead of me,
you know, which is one of the reasons we
were able to get two years done. Uh, you
know, I I uh I love it. Hopefully I
answer your question.
>> How well did you get to know Brian Cook
as a as a rookie and what's he going to
bring to this locker room? Yeah. No,
he's going to bring a ton of great
energy. Uh he's a fierce competitor. He
loves the game. Uh you know, he's he's
got he's got a he's got a lot of
personality. Just got to get it out of
him a little bit. Might take a little
time, but I remember uh when he first
got to Kansas City, he was immediately
uh in the mix, you know, and in terms of
just being a guy in the locker room that
vets respected. Uh he worked his tail
off. He's he's he's about his business.
>> How much have you faced Maf?
>> Uh
Yeah. Uh 2023, uh I think we played them
here. Um I didn't have many snaps
against him, but I will tell you,
studying the film that year, uh really
special, like really special. Like, uh
just in terms of his burst, he had has a
great inside move. Uh he does a great
job with his hands, um transition, uh in
his rushes. Um, you know, I haven't
necessarily watched a ton of film film
on him last year, but what I did see, I
mean, you know, that that
potential is still there and even more
now.
>> Did the process of representing yourself
[clears throat] make you like is that a
potential thing you'd be interested in
doing when you're playing done playing
football is representing football
players or you're not you're not there
yet? [snorts]
>> Yeah. No, I'm not. I'm not to be honest.
I like outside of of doing this, I
really haven't put too much thought into
post uh football. You know, maybe call
me delusional, but I look forward to
doing this till I'm 40. So, um but I
haven't put too much thought into it and
and uh you know, I can't say never, but
um no, not necessarily.
>> Do you have to get certified to do that
to represent yourself?
>> Uh you don't. No, you don't. Yeah, it's
um it's as easy as walking up there to
Mike Brown and saying, "Hey, can we get
this done?
>> [laughter]
>> Yes, it is. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Appreciate you guys. Thank you. Thank
you guys.
>> [music]